A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2 FA925
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Editorial Correspondence, 2
  - GP #5089: Mitsuo Tabata and Daniel L. Alkon (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - GP #5090: Joseph Patlak and Richard Horn (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - GP #5091: Richard J. Paul, 1981 May 15 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - GP #5092: A.S. Verkman, James A. Dix and A.K. Solomon (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - GP #5093: Louis Simchowitz, Isaias Spilberg and Paul DeWeer (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - GP #5094: Brenda R. Eisenberg and Robert S. Eisenberg (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - GP #5095: D.J. Adams, W. Nonner, T.M. Dwyer and B. Hille, 1981 May 26 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - GP #5096: Philip Palade and Julio Vergara (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - GP #5097: J. T. Van Bruggen, Brent Chalmers and Mertie Muller (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - GP #5098: Sergio Grinstein, Ann DuPre and Aser Rothstein (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - GP #5099: M. Zamir, 1981 May 19 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - GP #5100: Jun-ichi Toyoda and Toru Kujiraoka, 1981 May 29 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - GP #5101: B. Eleazar Cohen (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - GP #5102: Gladys Escalona de Motta, J. del Castillo, M. De Leon and F. Cordoba (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - GP #5103: Jean Marc Dubois and Martin F. Schneider (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - GP #5104: J. Brahm (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - GP #5105: Robert S. Kass, Todd Scheuer and Kevin J. Malloy (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - GP #5016: Timothy H. Goldsmith and Thomas W. Cronin (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - GP #5107: Barry M. Millman, 1981 June 16 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - GP #5108: M. Deric Bownds, J. Hermolin, H.E. Ham and M.A. Karell (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - GP #5109: C.R. Scheid and F.S. Fay, 1981 June 19 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - GP #5110: J.O. Wieth, P.J. Bjerrum and C. L. Borders Jr., 1981 June 22 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - GP #5111: Sadao Sasaki, Ikuko Nakagaki, Hirohiko Mori, yusuke Imai and Masataka Murakami, 1981 June 25 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - GP #5112: Thomas G. Holmes, Robert E. Ten Eick and Laura Robertson (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - GP #5113: Angela F. Dulhunty (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - GP #5114: R.C. Jacobson, R. Tirosh, M.J. Delay and G.H. Pollack (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - GP #5115: Isao Inoue, 1981 July 1 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - GP #5116: Roberto Coronado and Christopher Miller, 1981 July 2 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - GP #5117: A.S. Verkman and A.K. Solomon (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - GP #5118: Kooichi Saida, 1981 July 7 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - GP #5119: Philip W. Brandt, Robert N. Cox, Masataka Kawai and T. Robinson (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - GP #5120: Salviati, M.M. Sorenson and A.B. Eastwood, 1981 July 9 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - GP #5121: F. Mekata (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - GP #5122: R.B. Muri (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - GP #5123: R.B. Muri and G.J. Jones (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - GP #5124: Michael L. Jennings (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - GP #5125: Setsuko Nagahama, Yonosuke Kobatake and Kenzo Kurihara (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - GP #5126: G. K. Strother and John E. Farr, 1981 July 17 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - GP #5127: Scott J. Sherman and William A. Catterall (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - GP #5128: C. William Davis and Arthur L. Finn (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - GP #5129: John A. Faulkner, Denis R. Claflin, Kevin K. McCully and David A. Jones (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - GP #5131, 5132, 5133: Evan Dick and Robert F. Miller (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - GP #5131, 5132, 5133: Evan Dick and Robert F. Miller (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - GP #5134: Jose A.L. Arruda, Sandra Sabatini and Christof Westenfelder (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - GP #5135: D.G. Shoemaker and P.K. Lauf, 1981 July 31 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - GP #5136: Ann S. Hobbs (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - GP #5137: Anne Walter, David Hastings and John Gutknecht (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - GP #5138: Christopher Miller (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - GP #5139: Stuart Thompson (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - GP #5140: W.J. Moody Jr., and S. Hagiwara (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - GP #5141: R. Igor Gamow (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - GP #5142: J.R. Hume and W. Giles (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - GP #5143: Fumio Kukita (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - GP #5144: John W. Peterson, III (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - GP #5145: Daniel A. Nachshen and Mordecai P. Blaustein (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - GP #5146: Samuel Cukierman and Antonio Paes (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - GP #5147: Joey L. Trantham, David J. Browning, Augustus O. Grant and Harold C. Strauss (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - GP #5148: William Frank Gilly and Clay M. Armstrong, 1981 September 1 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - GP #5149: William Frank Gilly and Clay M. Armstrong (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - GP #5150: Richard L. Lieber, Yin Yeh and Ronald J. Baskin (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - GP #5151: Beth Brunside, Michael Evans, R. Theodore Fletcher and G.J. Chader (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - GP #5152: Joseph C. Besharse, Daiga A. Dunis and Beth Burnside (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - GP #5153: Jun Asayama and Lincoln E. Ford (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - GP #5154: Ludwig Fischer and Ernst Florey (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - GP #5155: Michael Lucas (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - GP #5156: Martin Wilson, Frank S. Werblin and David Attwell, 1981 September 21 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - GP #5157: Michael D. Stern, Arthur A. Kort, Gopal M. Bhatnager and Edward G. Lakatta (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - GP #5158: J.C. Ellory and J.S. Willis, 1981 September 23 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - GP #5159: Giuseppe Galasso (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - GP #5160: T.J. McManus and Mark Haas (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - GP #5161: Jesper Brahm (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - GP #5162: K.L. Magleby and J.E. Zengel (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - GP #5163: K.L. Magleby and J.E. Zengel (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - GP #5164: K.L. Magleby and J.E. Zengel (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - GP #5165: Peter R. Brink, 1981 October 20 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - GP #5166: Christopher J. Lynch and Richard C. Deth (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - GP #5167: Michael L. Woodruff, Gordon L. Fain and Bruce L. Bastian, 1981 November 4 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - GP #5168: Michael L. Woodruff and Gordon L. Fain (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - GP #5169: Christopher J. Lynch and Richard C. Deth (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - GP #5170: L. Goldman and J.L. Kenyon (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - GP #5171: M. Tsacopoulos and S. Poitry (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - GP #5172: S.M. Sims, E.E. Daniel and R.E. Garfield (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - GP #5172 (rev.): S.M. Sims, E.E. Daniel and R.E. Garfield (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - GP #5173: S.M. Sims, E.E. Daniel and R.E. Garfield (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - GP #5174: Jenny J.L. Ho and S.S. Rothman (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - GP #5175: Rhoda Blostein, Pierre Drapeau, Stephen Benderofff and Andreq Weigensberg (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - GP #5176: Henry J. Mlekoday, Richard Moore and David G. Levitt (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - GP #5177: Robert R. Maynard and David G. Levitt, 1981 November 23 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - GP #5178: David G. Levitt and Henry J. Mlekoday (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - GP #5179: Robert E. Sheridan and Henry A. Lester, 1981 September 24 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - GP #5180: Philip A. Knauf, Foon-Yee Law and Pamela M. Marchant, 1981 November 24 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - GP #5181: Albert J. D?Alonzo and Joseph J. McArdle (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - GP #5182: Simon Gagne and Rejean Plamondon (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - GP #5183: Dale Sanders and Clifford Slayman (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - GP #5184: Olaf S. Andersen and Robert U. Muller (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - GP #5185: Robert U. Muller, Olaf S. Andersen (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - GP #5186: Yasunori Kakuta (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - GP #5187: Meyer B. Jackson, Harold Lecar, Valerie Arkansas and W. King Engel (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - GP #5188: Madison S. Spach, J. Mailer Kootsey and Joseph D. Sloan (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - GP #5189: Shey-Shing Sheu and Harry A. Fozzard, 1981 December 8 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - GP #5190: Geraldine Waloga and M.W. Bitensky, 1981 December 11 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - GP #5191: R. Igor Gamow and Barbel Botter, 1981 December 11 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - GP #5192: Ralph Zuckerman, Geoffrey J. Schmidt and Stan M. Dacko (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - GP #5193: Ruth E. Wachtel and Wilkie A. Wilson (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - GP #5194: W.R. Levick, L.N. Thibos, T. Cohn, D.C. Catanzaro and H.B. Barlow (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - GP #5195: Michihisa Miyake and Kenzo Kurihara (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - GP #5196: Koichi Ozaki, Reiko Hara and Tomiyuri Hara (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - GP #5197: Michael T. Crow and Martin J. Kushmerick (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - GP #5198: Dale J. Benos and Ramon Latorre (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - GP #5199: Louis L. Odette and Peter H. Hartline (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - GP #5200: Louis L. Odette and Peter H. Hartline (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - GP #5201: K.A.P. Edman, G. Elizinga and M.I.M. Noble (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - GP #5202: Bernardo Rudy, B. Kirschenbaum and L.A. Green (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - GP #5203: N. Suzan Nadi and Thomas Getchell 1/11/82 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - GP #5204: N. Suzan Nadi and Thomas Getchell 1/11/82 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - GP #5205: W.H. Miller (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - GP #5206: Donald T. Campbell (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - GP #5207: Judith A. Heiny and Julio Vergara (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - GP #5208: Suechika Suzuki and Haruo Sugi (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - GP #5209: Seishi Kato, Toshiyasu Ogaswara and Takuro Osa (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - GP #5210: S. Grindstein, C.A. Clarke, A. Dupre and A. Rothstein (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - GP #5211: D. Mentrard, G. Vassort and R. Fischmeister, 1982 January 27 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - GP #5212: Joseph R. Stimers and Lou Byerly (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - GP #5213: C.M. Armstrong, R.P. Swenson, Jr. and S. R. Taylor (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - GP #5214: Jack H. Kaplan (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - GP #5215: Julio Vergara and Carlo Caputo (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - GP #5216: P.N. Kao, M.R. James-Kracke and C.Y. Kao (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - GP #5217: James Watras, Sharon Glezen, Christiana Seifert (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - GP #5218: Paul Witkovsky and Chen-Yu Yang (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - GP #5219: Steven A. Weinman and Luis Reuss (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - GP #5220: Walter F. Boron and Emile L. Boulpaep (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - GP #5221: Walter F. Boron and Emile L. Boulpaep, 1982 February 16 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - GP #5222: Peter A. Friedman and Thomas E. Andreoli (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - GP #5223: Neal Shepherd (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - GP #5224: James W. Clack and David R. Pepperberg, 1982 February 17 (Box 90, Folder 7)